<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Itagui</string>
    <string name="titleAdvertising">¡Welcome to Itagüí!</string>
    <string name="titleAbout">About</string>
    <string name="text1Advertising">Itagui, a safe and active city, which has a large commercial and recreational sector; a welcoming city where you can enjoy its renewed parks, nature of its judges and the various entertainment venues. Come and live it!</string>
    <string name="titleHotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="text1Hotels">Hotel Ruiseñor has 25 years of experience in business service, tourism and family. It is located in the heart of Itagui close to large industrial and commercial complexes: Banks, Clinics, Hospitals, Churches and most importantly the Metro.</string>
    <string name="text2Hotels">HOTEL ALCARAVAN has 96 rooms for 1, 2 or 3 beds, covered parking for free, laundry service, restaurant, room service, Internet, WIFI, coffee, bar, Wet Area, Jacuzzi, Turkish, board games , billiards and an excellent view of the city. Located in a strategic point of the city, at Carrera 50A number 84-09, adjacent to the wholesale center, 5 minutes from the South Terminal and Olaya Herrera Airport, near the station Ayurá metro and center clothing and fashion.</string>
    <string name="text3Hotels">The hotel is located in the industrial city of Colombia (Itagüí), large business sector. We have 102 comfortable rooms and modern facilities. The Central Hotel Plaza is the most elegant and best care of the whole area. We are in the midst of shopping centers near the Metro Ayurá, fun sites, banks, and easy access to neighboring municipalities station: Envigado and Sabaneta; Also just 15 minutes from the Zona Rosa of Medellin and 20 minutes from the Convention Center, the capital of Antioquia, Plaza Mayor.</string>
    <string name="button_return">Return</string>
    <string name="titleBars">Bars</string>
    <string name="text1Bars">Located in a strategic area of the Municipality of Itagui LA FONDA MALAGUEÑA is a beautiful corner to come, share and enjoy the ideal place to celebrate and hang out outside the routine. We will wait for you!</string>
    <string name="text2Bars">Mi Pueblo: The best representation of a roadside inn in times of "upa" framed by the characteristics of a mountaineer people and characters of yesteryear. Canahuate: An ancient site, with the most amazing decor of the Old West, where they take life Indians, cowboys, carriages and various adventures at the best western style.</string>
    <string name="text3Bars">Enjoy the scenery and atmosphere Antioqueño embodied in the essence that surrounds it as the artistic charms it has to tell the story of our people put before their eyes. The structure and decoration Bitaguí Fonda is a memorial of the cultural wealth, memories of a Itaguí during the year 1919, where paintings and photographs are highly valued for their antiquity.</string>
    <string name="titleTourist">Tourist Sities</string>
    <string name="text1Tourist">A mountain thinking. Who would believe ... And a space where you get to dream, to laugh, clap and, in the best case, to hug, hold hands and reconcile with the neighbor, the friend who one day he walked away from the confrontation or with which they have shared experiences, neglect, abandonment.</string>
    <string name="text2Tourist">Ditaires is a traditional upper-middle class neighborhood of the city of Itagui, Colombia.1 It was named in honor of Benedikta zür Nieden known as Dona Dita, wife of Diego Echevarria Misas, Itagüi businessman philanthropist who donated much of his money to Aburrá Valley municipalities. In the neighborhood are the Casa de la Cultura Itagui, the Estadio Metropolitano Ciudad de Itagüí Itagui and the Coliseum. Its main feature is its greenery and peaceful coexistence of its inhabitants, most of whom are employees of major companies and Itagui students.</string>
    <string name="text3Tourist">The town is the center of fashion in Colombia is called Itagui. wholesale and retail buyers from different cities travel long distances to get to this place that hides in himself the best in apparel and textiles. Since October commercial warehouses begin preparations. It all starts with the increase in staff, remodeling of the premises, the purchase of goods and conducting promotional strategies of products.</string>
    <string name="titleDemography">Demography</string>
    <string name="text1Demography">Population: 258,520 inhabitants. Population density: 13,545 inhabitants per square kilometer. Men: 47.2% Women: 52.8%. Illiteracy for over 5 years: 4.9%. Electricity coverage: 98.9%. Aqueduct: 97.5%. Telephony: 94.7%. socioeconomic status: 1: 6.0%, 2: 41.7%, 3: 51.2%, 4: 1.1%. Ethnography: Mestizos and whites: 93.9%, Afrocolombianos: 6.1%.</string>
    <string name="text1About">Itagüí v. 1.1.0 - 05042016.</string>
    <string name="text2About">Juan David Jiménez García. All rights reserved.</string>
</resources>